webitcongress.com 2019-07-11

# 

Webit Foundation has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.webit.org

Webit Foundation reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement.

Webit Foundation respects your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the type of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.webit.org and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.  Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, you have the choice not to use our Website. 

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website

  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

  * From your registration for our events

  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.

**Who we are**

Webit stands for a global community and a series of events, the largest of which welcomes over 15 000 attendees from 110 countries.

The Webit Global Community consists of over 100 000 digirati, policy makers, innovators, entrepreneurs, investors, scientists and experts fascinated by technology and fostering the digital transformation in the business and the society.

The annual events' locations include Istanbul(Webit.EMEA), Dubai (Webit.MENA), Singapore (Webit.APAC), New Delhi (Webit.INDIA) and Sofia (Webit.Festival EUROPE) thus bridging digital Europe, Middle East, Africa and Asia.

Webit.Foundation is committed to boosting the entrepreneurial ecosystem in EMEA and Asia and improving the state of innovation for a better future. Annually, we grant over $1 million to startups from all around the world through our Founders Games and also providing awards of over €200 000 for the winning startup.

During the years, Webit remained committed to one very important thing - creating happiness. We believe that happiness is where people are successful while staying together with their family and friends.

We are achieving this goal by creating a density of opportunities and bringing the top entrepreneurs, investors, enterprise leaders, academia and policy makers from all around the world to the locations where we are needed.

**Collection of Personal Data**

Under the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) personal data is defined as: 

“any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('data subject'); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person”.

By "Usage Information" or "Usage Data" we mean information about an individual’s online activity that, by itself, does not identify the individual, such as browser type, operating system, top viewed and visited pages and links on our web site, top entry and exit points, number of form completions, time spent on pages, top downloads, top keywords used offsite to lead customers to our website, information collected via cookies, and other device event information such as system activity, crashes, and hardware settings.

Generally, we do not consider Usage Data as Personal Information because Usage Data by itself usually does not identify an individual. Personal Information and Usage Data may be linked together. Different types of Usage Information also may be linked together and, once linked, may identify an individual person. In such cases it is treated and protected as Personal Data. Also, some Usage Data may be Personal Information under applicable law.

Webit Foundation collects information that you provide to us and from your use of the Website and the services. The information that we collect and how we process it depends on how you use and access the Website. Some information is collected automatically through the use of cookies and similar data collection tools. Please see below for more information on Webit Foundation's use of cookies.

We collect information from you when you

**Use the Website:  **We collect Personal Information and Usage Data from you when you create an account to use one of the services, contact us for help or information or otherwise provide your Personal Information, or request other services. We collect the information and content that you submit to us when you input your information in a form on our website, request additional information on a service, and when you enter comments or submit a review or complaint.

**Connect with Social Media though the Website:  **The Website may offer you the ability to use Facebook Connect or other social media services (collectively, “Social Media”) in conjunction with certain services. When you access the services through your Facebook or other Social Media account, the services may, depending on your privacy settings, have access to information that you have provided to the Social Media platform. We may use this information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or at the time the information was collected. 

**Usage Data:**  We also automatically collect Usage Data when you interact with the Website. Whenever you use the Website or the services, we use the location information from your mobile device or browser to tailor the services and website experience to your location.

**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.**

As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.

  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.

  * Speed up your searches.

  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies.**  A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and other technologies and how to manage their use. If you elect to refuse or delete cookies, you will need to repeat this process if you use another computer, or change browsers.

  * **Flash Cookies.**  Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies.

  * **Web Beacons.**  Pages of our Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

We do not collect personal information automatically, but we may tie this information to personal information about you that we collect from other sources or you provide to us.

**Third Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Website are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

**How We Use Your Personal Data**

We use the Personal Data that we collect to operate, improve, and personalize the Website and services including to provide customer service, customize our marketing, to detect, prevent and mitigate fraudulent or illegal activities. You agree that we may use your Personal Data as follows:

  * to provide the services to you;

  * to fulfil any other purpose for which you provided it;

  * to operate, improve and personalize the services we offer, and to give each user a more consistent and personalized experience when interacting with us;

  * for customer service, security, to detect fraud or illegal activities, or and for archival and backup purposes in connection with the provision of the Services;

  * to communicate with you, either via email, telephone, or otherwise as authorized by you to inform you about the Services, Conferences, Events, etc.. 

  * to better understand how users access and use the website and services, for the purposes of trying to improve the Website and services and to respond to user preferences, including language and location customization, personalized help and instructions, or other responses to users' usage of the services;

  * to help us develop our new services and improve our existing services;

  * to provide users with advertising and direct marketing that is more relevant to you;

  * to assess the effectiveness of and improve advertising and other marketing and promotional activities on or in connection with the Services.

  * for any other purpose with your consent.

**Legal Basis for The Processing of Personal Data from EEA Residents**

If you reside within the European Economic Area (EEA), our processing of your personal information will be legitimized as follows: 

  * Whenever we require your consent for the processing of your personal information such processing will be justified pursuant to Article 6(1) lit. (a) of the General Data Protection Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (“GDPR”). 

  * If the processing of your personal data is necessary for the performance of a contract between you and Webit Foundation or for taking any pre-contractual steps upon your request, such processing will be based on GDPR Article 6(1) lit. (b).”). If this data is not processed, Webit Foundation will not be able to register you for a selected event. 

  * Where the processing is necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation, we will process your information on basis of GDPR Article 6(1) lit. (c)

  * And where the processing is necessary for the purposes of Webit Fondation’s legitimate interests, such processing will be made in accordance with GDPR Article 6(1) lit. (f). “Legitimate Interests” means the interests of our company in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best service and and most secure experience. For example, we have an interest in making sure our events are relevant for you, so we may process your personal data to send you information that is tailored to your interests. It can also apply to processing that is in your interests as well.

For example, we may process your information to protect you against fraud when transacting on our website, and to ensure our websites and systems are secure.

When we process your personal information for our legitimate interests, we make sure to consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative), and your rights under data protection laws. Our legitimate business interests do not automatically override your interests - we will not use your Personal Data for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).

**Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our affiliates.

  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal data confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

  * With your consent.

  * For legal purposes: We also may share information that we collect from users, as needed, to enforce our rights, protect the rights, property or safety of others, or as needed to support external auditing, compliance and corporate governance functions. We will disclose Personal Data as we deem necessary to respond to a subpoena, regulation, binding order of a data protection agency, legal process, governmental request or other legal or regulatory process. We may also share Personal Information as required to pursue available remedies or limit damages we may sustain.

  * Corporate Changes. We may transfer information, including your Personal Data, in connection with a merger, sale, acquisition or other change of ownership or control by or of us or any affiliated company (in each case whether in whole or in part). When one of these events occurs, we will use reasonable efforts to notify users before your information is transferred or becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

**Where We Store Your Personal Data**

The data we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored in the European Union in the Republic of Bulgaria. Webit Foundation will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. All information you provide to Webit Foundation is stored on secure servers. Where you have chosen a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorized access.

**Transfers to countries outside the EU and EEA**

We do not transfer any personal data of EU citizens outside EU/EEA

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

If you wish to confirm that Webit Foundation is processing your personal data, or to have access to the personal data Webit Foundation may have about you, or have other questions, please contact us at through our [Data Subject Access Portal](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/e5be5ff5-ff51-4a7b-a271-ea2f71b89d29)  or via [DPO@amatas.eu](mailto:DPO@amatas.eu)

You may also request information through our about: the purpose of the processing; the categories of personal data concerned; who else outside Webit Foundation might have received the data from Webit Foundation; what the source of the information was (if you did not provide it directly to Webit Foundation); where the personal data is stored and how long it will be stored. You have a right to correct the record of your personal data maintained by Webit Foundation if it is inaccurate. You may request that Webit Foundation erase that data or cease processing it, subject to certain exceptions. You may also ask Webit Foundation for your personal data to be supplemented or updated, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. You may withdraw your consent for the processing of personal data or the further processing of personal data by Webit Foundation at any time.  You may also request that Webit Foundation cease using your data for direct marketing purposes. You have a right to lodge a complaint with the appropriate data protection authority if you have concerns about how Webit Foundation processes your personal data. When technically feasible, Webit Foundation will—at your request—provide your personal data to you or transmit it directly to another controller. You have the right to receive your personal information in a structured and standard format.

Reasonable access to your personal data will be provided at no cost to Webit Foundation members, conference attendees and others upon request made to Webit Foundation at via the [Data Subject Access Portal ](https://app-de.onetrust.com/app/#/webform/e5be5ff5-ff51-4a7b-a271-ea2f71b89d29) or [DPO@amatas.eu](mailto:DPO@amatas.eu). If access cannot be provided within a reasonable time frame, or, for some reason, access is denied, Webit Foundation will provide an explanation as to why access has been denied. In such cases you also have the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority: Commission for Personal Data Protection of the Republic of Bulgaria, www. cpdp.bg. 

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. You may also contact is through our contact form to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us.

**Questions, Concerns or Complaints**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Notice, please [contact us](http://www.webit.org/contact.php)
